[Music]
Hello friends welcome to Prayag News Techni,
today in this video we are going to tell you
about some bad news from Airtel, yes,
recently
a new statement has come from the chairman of Airtel
in which there is bad news for Airtel users,
if you are an Airtel customer and
you use Airtel SIM then
this can be bad news for you
because Airtel has recently announced
that they are going to increase their plans,
yes in the new statement from Airtel,
Chairman Sunil
Bharti Mittal has said that soon we are going to
increase the plans of Airtel
and the recharge plans will now become expensive
because the company as of now is
running in loss,
Indian Airtel may face a big loss in the telecom sector,
after which Airtel will soon
increase its plans in the middle of this year and as per
earlier the plans will now cost you more, for example earlier it used to cost
239, so
now almost
thank you, we will meet you in the next video